

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

502 13th Avenue E, Apt. 316, Seattle, Washington, 98102

□ (314) 954-4128 | ■jerry.belton@gmail.com | # completelymango.com | □ completelymango | □ completelymango

"Change is good."

#### About Me

Software Engineer with over 5 years of experience in the industry. Excells when working with a small agile teams and can communicate ideas and requirements effectively with stakeholders of differing technical backgrounds. Highly capable in developing programs in Python and Java (with significant Android experience) as well as C / C++. Always willing to learn new languages and tools. Enjoys spending free time working on personal programming projects.

### Education

#### **Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology**

Terre Haute, IN

B.S. IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

· Selected Coursework: Software Architecture and Design, Computer Networks, Artificial Intelligence, Computer Security

Aug. 2007 - May 2011

#### **University of Washington**

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Seattle, WA

Aug. 2015 - PRESENT

Selected Coursework: Artificial Intelligence

# **Experience**

### **Amazon - Device Advertising Products**

Seattle, WA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER - TEST

Aug. 2013 - Present

- Developed an Android application to communicate with other 1st party Kindle applications and assist several internal Kindle Advertising teams with their daily tasks.
- Coordinated with a small team of engineers to develop an automation framework for executing test cases on various devices, from FireTV to Kindle tablets running different operating systems.
- Developed and maintained automated test suites in a continuous deployment pipeline for our backend services that create and send ads to millions of devices each day.
- Drove several high-profile metrics processing issues to a close by constructing SQL queries to analyze production data in a unique way.

Rockwell Collins Cedar Rapids, IA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

May 2011 - Aug. 2013

- Coordinated with a team of engineers to implement feature requests in a C / C++ based software application; a graphics engine running on aircraft cockpit displays.
- · Developed several tools written in Python and Java to assist end-users efficiently build new graphics elements.
- · Successfully coordinated with teams in India and France to debug issues in their development environments.

# **Projects**

#Beer\_Tapp

http://107w.io/

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Jan. 2016 - PRESENT

• Worked with a group of talented engineers to develop 107w.io; a website designed to help users choose a beer from the tap list at a bar, given a list of beers that the user previously enjoyed.

**Completely Mango** 

http://completelymango.com

CREATO

Oct. 2014 - PRESENT

• Developed a personal website to post progress updates on projects, and acts as a server for chromecast and other test applications.

## **Skills**

Programming

Java, Python, C/C++, GoLang, Julia, OpenGL, Vulkan

Web

HTML, Javascript, Django with Python

**Applications** 

Appium (automation framework), Android, Chromecast, Linux (bash, vim, grep)

October 22, 2016 Jerry C. Belton · Résumé